Search. Destroy. Defend
Frogmen Operation Stormbringer is a action film
directed by Franklin A. Vallette.
Captain Rick Jeffries is the head of a group of elite soldiers who swim
into action, doing the dirty jobs no else can or wants to do.
They are in pursuit of a world traveling terrorist known only as Casper,
and have the difficult job of bringing him back--alive.
Rick, played by Tyler Christopher.
Andreas / Casper, played by Bentley Mitchum.
Miller, played by John Simon Jones.
Baker, played by Gary Murphy.
Jacobs, played by George Stanchev.
Rogers, played by Atanas Srebrev.
Bentley Mitchum (born February 22, 1967) is an American actor who has appeared in about 40 films and TV series, including Sundance grand jury prize
winner Ruby in Paradise, The Man in the Moon, The Wonder Years, Conviction, Susie Q, Meatballs 4 and Demonic Toys and Shark Attack.
Bentley also became the first American actor to play lead in an
Indian Tamil film, Little John opposite Jyothika.